Pick up kettle
Pour kettle into pan
Turn off timer
Pour leeks into pan
Pick up leek
Set timer
Pick up lid
Pick up colander
Open washing machine door
Throw away fluff
Take out clothes
Put clothes in washer
Close door
Turn on washer
Set dials
Scoop washing powder
Put washing powder in washing machine
Turn off timer
Pour kale into pot
push down kale
throw away packaging
rinse hands
pick up pot lids
mix kale the into the water
mix kale
put lid on pots
put down spoon
adjust pots
pick up spoon
pick up knife on chopping boards
pick up item on floor
pick up colander
Rinse hands
Put soap on sponge
Wash knife
Wash knife handle
Rinse knife
Dry off knife
Put away knife
Rinse chopping block
Wash chopping block
Turn on tap
Rinse off chopping block
rinse off chopping block
put chopping block on drying rack
open cupboards
take out bowl
close cupboards
put down bowl
pick up spin
stir kale
put down lids
put down spin
pick up fork
put down forks
move bowls
open cupboards
take out soy sauce
Take out soy sauce
Open lid
Pour soy sauce
Adjust fossil
Put down soy sauce
Close bottle
Put away bottle
Close lid
Pick up chilli oil
Put down chili oil
Put back olive oil
Shut cupboard
[END SUBTITLE]